
ff: parsing domain file
domain 'RICORICO-BASE' defined
 ... done.
ff: parsing problem file
problem 'RICORICO-BASE-JOC1' defined
 ... done.



Cueing down from goal distance:    5 into depth [1]
                                   4            [1]
                                   3            [1]
                                   2            [1]
                                   1            [1]
                                   0            

ff: found legal plan as follows

step    0: ASIGNAR-MENU LUNES PAELLA SALMON-PLANCHA
        1: ASIGNAR-MENU MARTES PAELLA SALMON-PLANCHA
        2: ASIGNAR-MENU MIERCOLES PAELLA SALMON-PLANCHA
        3: ASIGNAR-MENU JUEVES PAELLA SALMON-PLANCHA
        4: ASIGNAR-MENU VIERNES PAELLA SALMON-PLANCHA
     

time spent:    0.00 seconds instantiating 70 easy, 0 hard action templates
               0.00 seconds reachability analysis, yielding 60 facts and 70 actions
               0.00 seconds creating final representation with 60 relevant facts
               0.00 seconds building connectivity graph
               0.00 seconds searching, evaluating 6 states, to a max depth of 1
               0.00 seconds total time

